{
  question: "Choose a, b, c, or d. \n Which of these plants are edible? \n a) stinging neddles b) wisteria c) tobacco d) rhododendron",
  answer: "a"
},
{
  question: "Choose a, b, c, or d. \n What is the longest number of days someone has survived without eating? \n a) 23 b) 46 c) 58 d)74",
    answer: "74"
},
{
  question: "Choose a, b, c, or d. \n What animal kills the most people in the US each year? \n a) deer b) mosquitos c) bats d) snakes",
    answer: "a"
}
]

const history = [{
  question: "Choose a, b, c, or d. \n following explorers reached the North Pole? \n a) Roald Amundsen b) Robert E. Peary c) William Barents d) Adam Sound",
  answer: "b"
},
{
  question: "Choose a, b, c, or d. \n History students are taught about the \"the fall of Constantinople\" in 1453. to who did it fall? \n a) Christian crusaders b) Mongol hordes c) Ottoman Turks d)Romans",
    answer: "c"
},
{
  question: "Choose a, b, c, or d. \n Catherine the Great ruled what country? \n a) England b) France c)  Germany d) Russia",
    answer: "d"
}
]

let i = prompt("jjnjjkn" )
console.log(i)


 {
        question: "Choose a, b, c, or d. \n What is the longest number of days someone has survived without eating? \n a) 23 b) 46 c) 58 d)74",
          answer: "74"
      },
      {
        question: "Choose a, b, c, or d. \n What animal kills the most people in the US each year? \n a) deer b) mosquitos c) bats d) snakes",
          answer: "a"
      }
    ] 
  },
  {
    theme: "History",
    questionArray:[
      {
        question: "Choose a, b, c, or d. \n following explorers reached the North Pole? \n a) Roald Amundsen b) Robert E. Peary c) William Barents d) Adam Sound",
        answer: "b"
      },
      {
        question: "Choose a, b, c, or d. \n History students are taught about the \"the fall of Constantinople\" in 1453. to who did it fall?survived without eating? \n a) Christian crusaders b) Mongol hordes c) Ottoman Turks d)Romans",
          answer: "c"
      },
      {
        question: "Choose a, b, c, or d. \n Catherine the Great ruled what country? \n a) England b) France c)  Germany d) Russia",
          answer: "d"
      }
    ]
  }
]
